  import { QuizQuestion } from "../classes/quizquestion";

export const QUESTIONS: QuizQuestion[] = [
    {
      id: 1,
      question: 'Which country won the first ever FIFA World Cup in 1930?',
      options: ['Brazil', 'Germany', 'Uruguay', 'Argentina'],
      correctAnswer: 'Uruguay',
    },
    {
      id: 2,
      question: 'Who is the all-time leading scorer in the UEFA Champions League?',
      options: ['Lionel Messi', 'Cristiano Ronaldo', 'Robert Lewandowski', 'Karim Benzema'],
      correctAnswer: 'Cristiano Ronaldo',
    },
    {
      id: 3,
      question: 'Which club has won the most English Premier League titles?',
      options: ['Manchester United', 'Liverpool', 'Chelsea', 'Arsenal'],
      correctAnswer: 'Manchester United',
    },
    {
      id: 4,
      question: 'What is the nickname of the Brazilian national football team?',
      options: ['La Albiceleste', 'Seleção', 'Die Mannschaft', 'Les Bleus'],
      correctAnswer: 'Seleção',
    },
    {
      id: 5,
      question: 'Who won the Ballon d’Or in 2022?',
      options: ['Lionel Messi', 'Karim Benzema', 'Robert Lewandowski', 'Kevin De Bruyne'],
      correctAnswer: 'Karim Benzema',
    },
    {
      id: 6,
      question: 'Which country hosted the 2018 FIFA World Cup?',
      options: ['Brazil', 'Russia', 'South Africa', 'Qatar'],
      correctAnswer: 'Russia',
    },
    {
      id: 7,
      question: 'What is the capacity of Wembley Stadium in London?',
      options: ['90,000', '80,000', '75,000', '100,000'],
      correctAnswer: '90,000',
    },
    {
      id: 8,
      question: 'Which footballer is known as "El Pibe de Oro"?',
      options: ['Diego Maradona', 'Pelé', 'Zinedine Zidane', 'Ronaldinho'],
      correctAnswer: 'Diego Maradona',
    },
    {
      id: 9,
      question: 'What is the official name of the MLS championship trophy?',
      options: ['MLS Cup', 'Soccer Shield', 'Championship Trophy', 'North American Cup'],
      correctAnswer: 'MLS Cup',
    },
    {
      id: 10,
      question: 'Who scored the famous “Hand of God” goal?',
      options: ['Diego Maradona', 'Lionel Messi', 'Cristiano Ronaldo', 'Pelé'],
      correctAnswer: 'Diego Maradona',
    }, {
      id: 11,
      question: 'Which country has won the most FIFA World Cups?',
      options: ['Germany', 'Italy', 'Brazil', 'Argentina'],
      correctAnswer: 'Brazil',
    },
    {
      id: 12,
      question: 'Who scored the fastest goal in World Cup history?',
      options: ['Cristiano Ronaldo', 'Hakan Şükür', 'Pele', 'Lionel Messi'],
      correctAnswer: 'Hakan Şükür',
    },
    {
      id: 13,
      question: 'Which club is known as "The Old Lady"?',
      options: ['Real Madrid', 'Juventus', 'Manchester United', 'Bayern Munich'],
      correctAnswer: 'Juventus',
    },
    {
      id: 14,
      question: 'In what year was the English Premier League founded?',
      options: ['1990', '1992', '1988', '1995'],
      correctAnswer: '1992',
    },
    {
      id: 15,
      question: 'Which player has the most assists in football history?',
      options: ['Lionel Messi', 'Cristiano Ronaldo', 'Xavi Hernandez', 'Kevin De Bruyne'],
      correctAnswer: 'Lionel Messi',
    },
    {
      id: 16,
      question: 'Which football team is known as "The Red Devils"?',
      options: ['Manchester United', 'Liverpool', 'Bayern Munich', 'AC Milan'],
      correctAnswer: 'Manchester United',
    },
    {
      id: 18,
      question: 'Which country won the 2020 UEFA European Championship (held in 2021)?',
      options: ['Italy', 'England', 'France', 'Portugal'],
      correctAnswer: 'Italy',
    },
    {
      id: 19,
      question: 'Which manager has won the most UEFA Champions League titles?',
      options: ['Zinedine Zidane', 'Carlo Ancelotti', 'Pep Guardiola', 'Alex Ferguson'],
      correctAnswer: 'Carlo Ancelotti',
    },
    {
      id: 20,
      question: 'Who is the youngest player to score in a FIFA World Cup?',
      options: ['Pelé', 'Kylian Mbappé', 'Lionel Messi', 'Michael Owen'],
      correctAnswer: 'Pelé',
    },
    {
      id: 21,
      question: 'Which team has won the most UEFA Champions League titles?',
      options: ['AC Milan', 'Liverpool', 'Real Madrid', 'Bayern Munich'],
      correctAnswer: 'Real Madrid',
    },
    {
      id: 22,
      question: 'Who holds the record for the most goals scored in a single calendar year?',
      options: ['Lionel Messi', 'Cristiano Ronaldo', 'Pelé', 'Robert Lewandowski'],
      correctAnswer: 'Lionel Messi',
    },
    {
      id: 25,
      question: 'Who is the most expensive footballer in transfer history?',
      options: ['Neymar', 'Kylian Mbappé', 'Cristiano Ronaldo', 'Philippe Coutinho'],
      correctAnswer: 'Neymar',
    },
    {
      id: 26,
      question: 'Which country is known as "The Clockwork Orange" in football?',
      options: ['Netherlands', 'Spain', 'Portugal', 'Italy'],
      correctAnswer: 'Netherlands',
    },
    {
      id: 27,
      question: 'Who scored the only goal in the 2010 FIFA World Cup Final?',
      options: ['Andres Iniesta', 'David Villa', 'Xavi Hernandez', 'Fernando Torres'],
      correctAnswer: 'Andres Iniesta',
    },
    {
      id: 29,
      question: 'Which African country was the first to qualify for a World Cup?',
      options: ['Nigeria', 'Egypt', 'Cameroon', 'South Africa'],
      correctAnswer: 'Egypt',
    },
    {
      id: 30,
      question: 'Who is the only player to win three FIFA World Cups?',
      options: ['Pelé', 'Zinedine Zidane', 'Diego Maradona', 'Franz Beckenbauer'],
      correctAnswer: 'Pelé',
    },
    {
      id: 31,
      question: 'Which club is nicknamed "The Gunners"?',
      options: ['Arsenal', 'Chelsea', 'Tottenham Hotspur', 'West Ham United'],
      correctAnswer: 'Arsenal',
    },
    {
      id: 32,
      question: 'Who is the youngest player to score in a UEFA Champions League match?',
      options: ['Ansu Fati', 'Kylian Mbappé', 'Lionel Messi', 'Jude Bellingham'],
      correctAnswer: 'Ansu Fati',
    },
    {
      id: 33,
      question: 'Which team won the first ever European Championship in 1960?',
      options: ['France', 'USSR', 'Spain', 'Italy'],
      correctAnswer: 'USSR',
    },
    {
      id: 34,
      question: 'Which goalkeeper holds the record for the most clean sheets in the English Premier League?',
      options: ['Peter Schmeichel', 'Petr Čech', 'David de Gea', 'Edwin van der Sar'],
      correctAnswer: 'Petr Čech',
    },
    {
      id: 35,
      question: 'Which country has produced the most Ballon d’Or winners?',
      options: ['Brazil', 'Germany', 'Argentina', 'Italy'],
      correctAnswer: 'Germany',
    },
    {
      id: 36,
      question: 'What is the official name of the French national football team?',
      options: ['La Albiceleste', 'Les Bleus', 'Die Mannschaft', 'Azzurri'],
      correctAnswer: 'Les Bleus',
    },
    {
      id: 37,
      question: 'Which player scored the "Goal of the Century" in the 1986 FIFA World Cup?',
      options: ['Lionel Messi', 'Diego Maradona', 'Pelé', 'Zinedine Zidane'],
      correctAnswer: 'Diego Maradona',
    },
    {
      id: 38,
      question: 'Which club plays its home matches at the Camp Nou?',
      options: ['Real Madrid', 'Atletico Madrid', 'Barcelona', 'Sevilla'],
      correctAnswer: 'Barcelona',
    },
    {
      id: 39,
      question: 'Who scored the winning goal for Portugal in the Euro 2016 Final?',
      options: ['Cristiano Ronaldo', 'Eder', 'João Moutinho', 'Nani'],
      correctAnswer: 'Eder',
    },
    {
      id: 40,
      question: 'Which African player won the Ballon d’Or in 1995?',
      options: ['Samuel Eto’o', 'George Weah', 'Didier Drogba', 'Roger Milla'],
      correctAnswer: 'George Weah',
    },
    {
      id: 41,
      question: 'Which country won gold in men’s football at the 2008 Olympics?',
      options: ['Brazil', 'Germany', 'Argentina', 'Spain'],
      correctAnswer: 'Argentina',
    },
    {
      id: 42,
      question: 'Who holds the record for the fastest hat-trick in Premier League history?',
      options: ['Sadio Mané', 'Sergio Agüero', 'Robbie Fowler', 'Wayne Rooney'],
      correctAnswer: 'Sadio Mané',
    },
    {
      id: 43,
      question: 'Which English club has won the most FA Cup titles?',
      options: ['Manchester United', 'Arsenal', 'Liverpool', 'Chelsea'],
      correctAnswer: 'Arsenal',
    },
    {
      id: 44,
      question: 'Which country did Zinedine Zidane represent in international football?',
      options: ['Italy', 'France', 'Algeria', 'Morocco'],
      correctAnswer: 'France',
    },
    {
      id: 45,
      question: 'What is the nickname of the Spanish national football team?',
      options: ['La Roja', 'La Albiceleste', 'Seleção', 'Azzurri'],
      correctAnswer: 'La Roja',
    },
    {
      id: 46,
      question: 'Which club won the treble (League, Domestic Cup, Champions League) in 1999?',
      options: ['Real Madrid', 'Bayern Munich', 'Manchester United', 'Barcelona'],
      correctAnswer: 'Manchester United',
    },
    {
      id: 47,
      question: 'Who was the captain of Spain during their 2010 FIFA World Cup victory?',
      options: ['Sergio Ramos', 'Xavi Hernandez', 'Iker Casillas', 'Andres Iniesta'],
      correctAnswer: 'Iker Casillas',
    },
    {
      id: 48,
      question: 'Which country won the Copa América in 2021?',
      options: ['Brazil', 'Argentina', 'Uruguay', 'Colombia'],
      correctAnswer: 'Argentina',
    },
    {
      id: 49,
      question: 'What is the name of the German football league?',
      options: ['Serie A', 'La Liga', 'Bundesliga', 'Ligue 1'],
      correctAnswer: 'Bundesliga',
    },
    {
      id: 50,
      question: 'Who is known as the "King of Football"?',
      options: ['Cristiano Ronaldo', 'Pelé', 'Lionel Messi', 'Diego Maradona'],
      correctAnswer: 'Pelé',
    },
    {
      id: 52,
      question: 'Who is the all-time top scorer in the English Premier League?',
      options: ['Alan Shearer', 'Wayne Rooney', 'Harry Kane', 'Sergio Agüero'],
      correctAnswer: 'Alan Shearer',
    },
    {
      id: 53,
      question: 'Which country hosted the first FIFA World Cup in 1930?',
      options: ['Brazil', 'Italy', 'Uruguay', 'Argentina'],
      correctAnswer: 'Uruguay',
    },
    {
      id: 54,
      question: 'What is the official ball of the FIFA World Cup 2022 called?',
      options: ['Telstar', 'Al Rihla', 'Jabulani', 'Brazuca'],
      correctAnswer: 'Al Rihla',
    },
    {
      id: 56,
      question: 'Who won the FIFA World Cup Golden Boot in 2018?',
      options: ['Kylian Mbappé', 'Harry Kane', 'Luka Modrić', 'Antoine Griezmann'],
      correctAnswer: 'Harry Kane',
    },
    {
      id: 57,
      question: 'Which country is nicknamed "The Indomitable Lions"?',
      options: ['Ghana', 'Cameroon', 'Ivory Coast', 'Nigeria'],
      correctAnswer: 'Cameroon',
    },
    {
      id: 58,
      question: 'Who is the youngest player to score in a FIFA World Cup?',
      options: ['Pele', 'Lionel Messi', 'Kylian Mbappé', 'Diego Maradona'],
      correctAnswer: 'Pele',
    },
    {
      id: 59,
      question: 'Which player has the most assists in the UEFA Champions League?',
      options: ['Lionel Messi', 'Cristiano Ronaldo', 'Xavi', 'Angel Di Maria'],
      correctAnswer: 'Cristiano Ronaldo',
    },
    {
      id: 60,
      question: 'Which country has won the most Copa América titles?',
      options: ['Brazil', 'Uruguay', 'Argentina', 'Chile'],
      correctAnswer: 'Uruguay',
    },
    {
      id: 61,
      question: 'What is the maximum number of goals scored by a player in a single FIFA World Cup?',
      options: ['13', '10', '9', '11'],
      correctAnswer: '13',
    },
    {
      id: 62,
      question: 'Which stadium is known as "The Theatre of Dreams"?',
      options: ['Anfield', 'Old Trafford', 'Camp Nou', 'Wembley Stadium'],
      correctAnswer: 'Old Trafford',
    },
    {
      id: 63,
      question: 'Which player has the most appearances in the FIFA World Cup?',
      options: ['Miroslav Klose', 'Lothar Matthäus', 'Diego Maradona', 'Paolo Maldini'],
      correctAnswer: 'Lothar Matthäus',
    },
    {
      id: 64,
      question: 'Who won the FIFA World Cup in 2006?',
      options: ['France', 'Italy', 'Brazil', 'Germany'],
      correctAnswer: 'Italy',
    },
    {
      id: 65,
      question: 'Which country is known as "The Pharaohs" in football?',
      options: ['Nigeria', 'Ghana', 'Egypt', 'Morocco'],
      correctAnswer: 'Egypt',
    },
    {
      id: 66,
      question: 'What is the name of Bayern Munich’s home stadium?',
      options: ['Signal Iduna Park', 'Allianz Arena', 'Olympiastadion', 'Volksparkstadion'],
      correctAnswer: 'Allianz Arena',
    },
    {
      id: 67,
      question: 'Which country won the FIFA U-20 World Cup in 2023?',
      options: ['Italy', 'Brazil', 'Uruguay', 'France'],
      correctAnswer: 'Uruguay',
    },
    {
      id: 68,
      question: 'Who was the top scorer in the 2014 FIFA World Cup?',
      options: ['Lionel Messi', 'James Rodríguez', 'Neymar', 'Thomas Müller'],
      correctAnswer: 'James Rodríguez',
    },
    {
      id: 70,
      question: 'What is the name of Liverpool FC’s anthem?',
      options: ['You’ll Never Walk Alone', 'We Are the Champions', 'Glory Glory', 'Fields of Anfield Road'],
      correctAnswer: 'You’ll Never Walk Alone',
    },
    {
      id: 71,
      question: 'Who was awarded the FIFA Best Men’s Player in 2021?',
      options: ['Lionel Messi', 'Robert Lewandowski', 'Cristiano Ronaldo', 'Kevin De Bruyne'],
      correctAnswer: 'Robert Lewandowski',
    },
    {
      id: 72,
      question: 'Which African country hosted the FIFA World Cup in 2010?',
      options: ['Nigeria', 'South Africa', 'Ghana', 'Egypt'],
      correctAnswer: 'South Africa',
    },
    {
      id: 75,
      question: 'Which country won the most recent European Championship?',
      options: ['Spain', 'England', 'Portugal', 'France'],
      correctAnswer: 'Spain',
    },
    {
      id: 76,
      question: 'Which player has won the most Ballon d’Or awards?',
      options: ['Lionel Messi', 'Cristiano Ronaldo', 'Johan Cruyff', 'Michel Platini'],
      correctAnswer: 'Lionel Messi',
    },
    {
      id: 77,
      question: 'Which club has won the most Serie A titles?',
      options: ['AC Milan', 'Inter Milan', 'Juventus', 'Roma'],
      correctAnswer: 'Juventus',
    },
    {
      id: 78,
      question: 'Which team is known as "Los Blancos"?',
      options: ['Barcelona', 'Real Madrid', 'Atletico Madrid', 'Sevilla'],
      correctAnswer: 'Real Madrid',
    },
    {
      id: 79,
      question: 'Who won the Golden Ball in the 2018 FIFA World Cup?',
      options: ['Luka Modrić', 'Antoine Griezmann', 'Kylian Mbappé', 'Eden Hazard'],
      correctAnswer: 'Luka Modrić',
    },
    {
      id: 80,
      question: 'Which country did Pelé represent?',
      options: ['Argentina', 'Brazil', 'Portugal', 'Uruguay'],
      correctAnswer: 'Brazil',
    },
    {
      id: 81,
      question: 'Which player has the most red cards in football history?',
      options: ['Sergio Ramos', 'Gerardo Bedoya', 'Roy Keane', 'Patrick Vieira'],
      correctAnswer: 'Gerardo Bedoya',
    },
    {
      id: 84,
      question: 'Which country won the gold medal in men’s football at the 2012 Olympics?',
      options: ['Brazil', 'Mexico', 'Spain', 'Argentina'],
      correctAnswer: 'Mexico',
    },
    {
      id: 85,
      question: 'Who is known as "El Fenomeno"?',
      options: ['Ronaldo Nazário', 'Lionel Messi', 'Zinedine Zidane', 'Cristiano Ronaldo'],
      correctAnswer: 'Ronaldo Nazário',
    },
    {
      id: 86,
      question: 'Who holds the record for most goals in a single Premier League season?',
      options: ['Alan Shearer', 'Mohamed Salah', 'Sergio Agüero', 'Wayne Rooney'],
      correctAnswer: 'Mohamed Salah',
    },
    {
      id: 87,
      question: 'Which country won the 1994 FIFA World Cup?',
      options: ['Italy', 'Brazil', 'Germany', 'Argentina'],
      correctAnswer: 'Brazil',
    },
    {
      id: 88,
      question: 'Which team is nicknamed "The Blues"?',
      options: ['Chelsea', 'Manchester City', 'Leicester City', 'Everton'],
      correctAnswer: 'Chelsea',
    },
    {
      id: 89,
      question: 'Who won the FIFA Puskás Award in 2022?',
      options: ['Cristiano Ronaldo', 'Lionel Messi', 'Marcin Oleksy', 'Mohamed Salah'],
      correctAnswer: 'Marcin Oleksy',
    },
    {
      id: 90,
      question: 'Which country has the nickname "The Three Lions"?',
      options: ['Germany', 'England', 'Netherlands', 'Italy'],
      correctAnswer: 'England',
    },
    {
      id: 91,
      question: 'What is the name of Barcelona’s famous youth academy?',
      options: ['La Fábrica', 'La Masia', 'Cantera', 'Escola'],
      correctAnswer: 'La Masia',
    },
    {
      id: 92,
      question: 'Which club has the most La Liga titles?',
      options: ['Real Madrid', 'Barcelona', 'Atletico Madrid', 'Valencia'],
      correctAnswer: 'Real Madrid',
    },
    {
      id: 93,
      question: 'Who scored the decisive penalty in the 2006 FIFA World Cup Final for Italy?',
      options: ['Francesco Totti', 'Marco Materazzi', 'Andrea Pirlo', 'Fabio Grosso'],
      correctAnswer: 'Fabio Grosso',
    },
    {
      id: 94,
      question: 'Which player has the record for the most hat-tricks in football history?',
      options: ['Cristiano Ronaldo', 'Pele', 'Lionel Messi', 'Josef Bican'],
      correctAnswer: 'Cristiano Ronaldo',
    },
    {
      id: 96,
      question: 'Who is the manager of Manchester City as of 2024?',
      options: ['Pep Guardiola', 'Jurgen Klopp', 'Carlo Ancelotti', 'Jose Mourinho'],
      correctAnswer: 'Pep Guardiola',
    },
    {
      id: 98,
      question: 'What was the final score in the 2022 FIFA World Cup Final?',
      options: ['4-2', '3-3 (4-2 pens)', '2-1', '3-2'],
      correctAnswer: '3-3 (4-2 pens)',
    },
    {
      id: 99,
      question: 'Which country is famous for the "Total Football" playing style?',
      options: ['Brazil', 'Netherlands', 'Germany', 'Italy'],
      correctAnswer: 'Netherlands',
    },
    {
      id: 100,
      question: 'Who is the youngest manager to win the UEFA Champions League?',
      options: ['Pep Guardiola', 'Jose Mourinho', 'Julian Nagelsmann', 'Luis Enrique'],
      correctAnswer: 'Pep Guardiola',
    }  
  ];
